nigerianbulletin.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Nigerian Bulletin | Nigerian Bulletin - Naija Trending News

At Nigerianbulletin.com, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of our visitors and community. We do not sell, rent or trade email lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes. Our Privacy Policy sets out in detail when and why we collect your personal information, how we use it, the limited conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure. Please take a few minutes to go through the information below 

This privacy policy sets out how Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd and services. This includes, but is not limited to, NigerianBulletin.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. 

Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd may change this policy as and when necessary. All registered members with an active account will be notified when the policies are changed.

## What information we collect

When using any products and services provided by Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd, we may require some or all of the following information:

  * name
  * address
  * telephone number
  * email address
  * domain / Uniform Resource Locator (URL) where the software will be installed

Additionally, whilst using the NigerianBulletin.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

## What we do with the information we collect

The information you provide to Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons: 

  * internal record keeping
  * access to the NigerianBulletin.com website, associated websites and sub-domains
  * account management
  * purchase confirmation and account reset
  * confirmation of email address for members of NigerianBulletin.com
  * sending notices and relevant communications

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. 

## How we use cookies and IP addresses

NigerianBulletin.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to fully use NigerianBulletin.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit NigerianBulletin.com and any associated websites and sub-domains may be stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

## Google Analytics

When someone visits www.NigerianBulletin.com we use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. 

## Links to other websites

NigerianBulletin.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd. 

Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd has no control over any external websites, therefore, clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

## Controlling your personal information

When using the NigerianBulletin.com, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

You are entitled to view, amend, or delete the personal information that we hold. Email your request to our data protection officer Chris at dpo@nigerianbulletin.com 

Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your information to send you security information, product updates from our direct partners, or other information pertaining to Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd, or your account.

If you discover any of the information Nigerian Bulletin / Xposure Connect Africa Ltd holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.
